

Suvhradip Ghosh

Computer Science Engineer

Phone: 8910754998

Address: SHY AMPUR BUDGE BUDGE

SHYAMPUR

Website: https://suvhradipghosh07.github.io/live/

Email: suvhradip@gmail.com

Hi, I am Suvhradip,

a student who is highly interested in Deep Learning and just loves to build AI products that can be used for the betterment of humanity (and in general). I currently am catching up with the fast-moving field of AI. Saying, I am interested in Deep Learning, Machine Learning, Reinforcement Learning, Computer Vision and NLP. I am also interested in building Web Applications & Cybersecurity and am highly skilled at Web Development and moderately skilled in Cyber Security. I have built quite a handful of applications that shows my Web Development Skills. And also experienced Developer with a demonstrated history of working in computer software technology. Skilled in Photography, Public Speaking, Networking, and Machine Learning. A strong business development professional.

EXPERIENCE

Indian Institutes of Science Education and Research

Sep 19- Current

Research Intern

Research Intern in Neuro Science

Analysed.in April 19- July 19

Machine Learning Intern

Analysed helps recruiters in human analytics through AI and provides them with virtual testing tools to lighten the burden of the struggle for both recruiters and job aspirants. Let's eliminate together the troubles witnessed in the recruitment process and uncover a one-stop solution to it

- AI Virtual Recruitment Project Developer

Google Developers Jan 22 - current

Developer Student Club Lead

Google collaborates with university students who are passionate about growing developer communities and support them with starting student clubs on their campuses.

Netwizard Python Instructor Intern	June 2018 - July 2018
Internshala Student Partner	Dec 2018 - Mar 2019
Scoiash	Dec 2017 to Feb 2018

Social Media Marketing Intern

EDUCATION

Techno India Batanagar

Aug 2017 - Aug 2021

Bachelor in Technology - Computer Science

Sarangabad high School

Mar 2015 - May 2017

Class XII

SKILLS

Technical Skills

C, Python, Scikit learn, Keras, Tensorflow, Deep Learning, Natural Language Processing, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Numpy, Pandas, Seaborn, Machine Learning, Nltk, Adobe Photoshop.

Non Technical Skills:

Photography, Painting, cooking

PROJECTS

Transfer Learning on Malaria Cell Dataset

https://github.com/suvhradipghosh07/Malaria-Detection-With-Deep-Learning-Various-Architecture

Malaria is a life-threatening disease caused by parasites that are transmitted to people through the bites of infected mosquitoes. Automation of the diagnosis process will enable accurate diagnosis of the disease and hence holds the promise of delivering reliable healthcare to resource-scarce areas. Machine learning technologies have been used for automated diagnosis of malaria.

Chest Pneumonia Detection using various Deep Learning Architecture

https://github.com/suvhradipghosh07/Chest-Pneumonia-Detection-using-Deep-Learning-Various-Architecture

Breast Cancer Detection using Various ML Algorithms

https://bit.ly/2GkCKcu

Augmented Random Search for Reinforcement Learning

https://github.com/suvhradipghosh07/Augmented-Random-Search

Augmented Random Search is a game-changing AI. It is very simple implementation it is able to do exactly the same thing that Google Deepmind did in there accomplishment last year which is to train an AI to work and run across a field. Augmented Random Search is 100x time faster and 100x time more powerful. The best part is that with augmented random search is no need for complex Algorithms or Framework such as Tensorflow or PyTorch. This is the best AI in 2018.

CERTIFICATIONS

Deep Learning & Neural Network

Coursera

Advanced Deep Learning

Coursera

Google Cloud Platform (GCP)

Coursera

HONORS

Celsius Hackathon 2019 1st Runner Up

Calcutta Institute of Engineering & Management

Project is Deep Learning based online web application for medical report analysis.

Nasa Space App Challenge Pre Qualifier

Nasa Space App Challenge

LANGUAGES |

English (Full professional), Hindi (Full professional), Bengali (Full professional)

RECOMMENDATIONS

Scott Dominguez

July 10, 2019

Office 365 Exchange Online Live Site SRE at Microsoft

All I can say is that Suvhradip is a highly motivated machine learning developer which is key to be a successful resource for any potential employer.

Sabyasachi Mukhopadhyay

March 18, 2019

Data Scientist|TEDx Speaker|Author|Top 50 Innovator|Public Speaker|Intel Software Innovator|Google Developer Expert ML

I know Suvhradip for last two years. While mentoring him for several deep learning related projects, I found that he has a very strong foundations on basic aspects of deep learning. He has a very good grip on Python, and can utilize the deep learning frameworks like tensorflow, pytorch quite effectively. My best wishes are with him regarding his bright future.

CONTRIBUTION

Github Account

https://github.com/suvhradipghosh07

Hackerrank

Python Programming Language

https://www.hackerrank.com/suvhradip